you know it's a good thing you guys
arrived today I mean
i was like
i was bored today so uh you know was
writing down the chain
i just happened to write down my top
five favorite
and the favorite soccer hand song
you got me here what could you do
i think maybe we should start with the
with
the words because we all know that's the
real reason you're here
so first of all oh
i will be at least five of my least
favorite songs
not in a specific order except for the
last one that one is so
bad yeah I know what you're thinking
wait table one two three four five
you actually have a least favorite Sonic
Underground song well that's right
i do
then you won't believe how bad that is
so I think my
number one like my number five for least
favorite soccer rounds
would be face your fears
now I know what you're thinking well
wait that's a good song well wait a
second why
wait
look at the scene everyone this is an
unedited scene from the official music
video
i know huh look at that
they actually think they can get away
with repeating like that
hell no I they they they sped it
up they they took that one seam and i
like spread it up flipped it to another
domination whatever they could do
to to to lengthen that saying
like God down
i I mean granted it's a good song we
we all know that but what you
gonna do
number four will be the song I found my
home
dvd
i actually love the song but
for those trolls you fans who
bought the soccer Underground dvd you
may have noticed
holy they butchered this song
what the did they do
well i'll tell you what they do if you
pay attention
then we move Sonia I stay with remove
Sonic voice from the
from the vocals all you can hear is
mannix
i mean now I agree maddie is an okay
singer but not if you're singing alone
if you hear the song if you hear the dvd
version of that song
I'm not even kidding smelly sounds like
he's got drumstick self-self out up his
ass
home is a place in your heart where
memories flow
number three for least favorite songs is
oh bear force me
hey you know what I think I can wait
i I i think instead of showing you the
music video
i can show you the whole music video
right now
oh bear four feet oh barefoot
oh barefoot I believe in our but
it's just that one line over and over
and over again
nothing else not only that but it's the
same
five second beat just looping for a
whole minute long
that's not if that's not if that doesn't
suck my
ass I don't know what does
number four for least favorite song
is part of the problem
stand up and show him what you got
now now do you honestly I think you
should know what's going on
episode Sonic Max so you just tried to
find the mom
just like every oh that's a that's right
hey hey how did you see your mama oh no
okay what about you no
will they run into this group of people
they ask hey have you guys seen our mama
this group of people is like oh so we
don't know
John mcSonia is then well can you help
us
look we think she may be around here
then they be like so we'll be there
right now
not to mention robotics said he will
kill our families if we you know
help help the resistance like young we
don't want to have families or anything
then Sonic Manic and Sonia they're like
crying saying
you know what if you don't help someone
when they're in me
then you're part of the problem terrible
then the sun kicks in I'm not even
joking everyone
this is actual that goes there
look at the scene look at it right now
do you know the man who was a prisoner
in this tower
maybe now they'll tell us who the
prisoner is
and now oh oh my God
now my number one least favorite song
in all the suck Underground
would have to be
don't be a bad saddle when nobody's
gonna like you
I'm not even kidding no that is act
after the line as stupid as it sounds
now the point of that one is bob will be
he betrayed he betrayed somebody sonja
he talked
no he even you are perfect he accidental
Robotnik
where the resistance cap was
accidentally
Sonia is an exotic man come on it was an
accident we gotta go help him
stalking mag is then like no we can't do
it he backs
at us Manic then says
yeah I even wrote a song then the song
plays
and then what happens after the song
they're like
okay God we done singing for the episode
let's go help our great
lover Sonic is even like oh I’ve got
i will bother
i mean I'm doing this take
take away the song and look at the scene
the before and after
scenes take away the song and look how
the scene goes instead
listen guys barbie needs our help look
Sonia
i know those arista butts are close
friends of yours but they're getting
what they deserve
and gossip always comes back to bite you
just like the song says
Sonic sagna not you
yeah that don't make Jack no no
anymore
damn
and that one was my top five
least favorite song from soccer around